

□+1 (734) 496-1803 | ■ jwnchung@umich.edu | ♠ jaewonchung.me | 回 jaywonchung

Summary _

I am a second year PhD student in CSE at the University of Michigan, advised by Professor Mosharaf Chowdhury. My research interest is in the intersection of software systems and deep learning, with a recent focus in energy consumption. I lead the ML Energy initiative (https://ml.energy).

Education

University of Michigan

Ann Arbor, MI, USA

Ph.D. STUDENT IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Sep 2021 - present

Seoul National University

B.S. IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Seoul, South Korea Mar 2015 - Aug 2021

- GPA: 4.04/4.3 (overall) 4.15/4.3 (major)
- Summa Cum Laude
- Period includes two years of military service, required to all Korean men.

Publications

- Zeus: Understanding and Optimizing GPU Energy Consumption of DNN Training, Jie You*, <u>Jae-Won Chung</u>* (*: co-primary authors), Mosharaf Chowdhury, Symposium on Networked Systems Design and Implementation (NSDI), 2023 (Acceptance rate = 18.38%)
- ShadowTutor: Distributed Partial Distillation for Mobile Video DNN Inference, Jae-Won Chung, Jae-Yun Kim, Soo-Mook Moon, International Conference on Parallel Processing (ICPP), 2020 (Acceptance rate = 28.99%)

Experience _____

SymbioticLab UMich, United States

GRADUATE STUDENT RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Sep 2022 - Present

- Advised by Professor Mosharaf Chowdhury.
- · Zeus. Discovered the trade-off between DNN training time and energy. Designed a Multi-Armed Bandit solution for time-energy optimization.
- Mentoring two MS students who work on expanding Zeus to various training scenarios.

Software Platform Lab SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN Apr 2020 - Jun 2022

- · Worked with Professor Byung-Gon Chun.
- Developed Crane, a GPU cluster manager for AutoML workloads.
- Built a Kubernetes backend for Crane that scaled to 288 GPUs.
- On-boarded and mentored six incoming interns and graduate students.

Virtual Machine and Optimization Lab

SNU, South Korea

SENIOR PROJECT

Dec 2019 - Jun 2020

· ShadowTutor: Server-client collaborative video DNN inference. Use of knowledge distillation reduced network data transfer by 95%.

Computer Vision Lab SNU, South Korea

Undergraduate Intern Jun 2019 - Dec 2019

· Better meta-initialization methods for Model-Agnostic Meta-Learning (MAML) with neural memory modules and convex programs.

Lab of Imaging Science and Technology

SNU, South Korea

Undergraduate Intern

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Designed and implemented a full deep learning pipeline for Quantitative Susceptibility Mapping, a vision task 3D MRI field data.

OCTOBER 13, 2022 JAE-WON CHUNG · RÉSUMÉ

Honors & Awards

Jul 2021 **Kwanjeong Overseas Scholarship,** Kwanjeong Educational Foundation, \$100,000 over four years
Mar 2019 **Kwanjeong Undergraduate Scholarship,** Kwanjeong Educational Foundation, \$20,000 over two years

Seoul, South Korea Seoul, South Korea

Teaching

- Spring 2021 Operating Systems, Main TA, Managed course projects and led group design reviews.
- Fall 2020 Computer Organization (Undergraduate architecture), Peer tutor, Provided 30 hours of online lecture, Best Tutor Award!

Skills

Language Python, Rust, CUDA, C++, Verilog, C, Bash

Framework PyTorch, Pandas, Matplotlib

Methodology Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Multi-Armed Bandit

Tool Docker, Kubernetes, LaTeX

English TOEFL 120 (Perfect score, Feb 2020), GRE 167/170/4.5 (Mar 2018), TOEIC 990 (Perfect score, Oct 2018)